This Town Will Eat You Alive.
Remains is a horror, science fiction film directed by Colin Theys.
The story centers on two lone survivors of a bizarre accident that
reduced most of the world's population to zombies.
They take refuge in a vacant casino and fight a
losing battle against the undead.
Tom, played by Grant Bowler.
Jensen, played by Miko Hughes.
Ramsey, played by Lance Reddick.
Cindy, played by Tawny Cypress.
Tori, played by Evalena Marie.
Victor, played by Anthony Marks.
Remains, also billed as Steve Niles' Remains, is a
2011 post-apocalyptic horror film.
It depicts a small group of people in a Reno, Nevada casino who have survived a nuclear
disaster while the rest of humanity has been turned into flesh eating zombies.
It was produced by the Chiller Network and is based on
the comic book series of the same name.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.